indianfaculty.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy - IndianFaculty.com

The Privacy Policy of our visitors to IndianFaculty.com is important to us. 

At IndianFaculty.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important.  
Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when  
you use and visit IndianFaculty.com, and how we safeguard your information.  
 We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files:  
As websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in log files include your Internet Protocol address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site IndianFaculty.com  
(such as Internet Explorer, Firefox etc.), the time you visited our site &  
which pages you visited throughout our site. 

Cookies and Web Beacons:  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit IndianFaculty.com. This could include only screening you a popup once in your visit,  
or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forum.

We also use third party advertisements on IndianFaculty.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site IndianFaculty.com, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense Program) information including your Internet Protocol address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or screening certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as screening cooking ads to someone who frequent cooking sites).

Google, as a third party vendor uses cookies to serve ads on our site IndianFaculty.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site's visitors based upon their visit to our site and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

You can decide to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings or by managing preferences in programs (such as Norton Internet Security).  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site IndianFaculty.com as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services / programs (such as logging into forums or accounts).

Links to Other Sites:  
IndianFaculty.com is not responsible for the content / practices of third party websites that may be linked to our Site. IndianFaculty.com may also be linked to websites operated by other companies. Visitors to these websites should refer to each website's respective privacy policies and practices.

IndianFaculty.com Children's Policy:  
We take care of privacy of children. We have our webpages for inspiration and appropriate for our younger viewers. We work toward increase your knowledge and interests.

Your Acceptance of These Terms:  
By using IndianFaculty.com website, you signify your acceptance of Privacy Policy our site. If you don't agree to site privacy policy, please don't use IndianFaculty.com website. IndianFaculty.com reserves the right to modify, change or otherwise update this policy at any time, so visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time to time.
